All ships, fall back!
Put distance between us so we don't get hit
by the light, and continue our assault!
MARIA, how are Shido, Tohka, and the others?
I still don't know.
That object is disrupting my visuals.
Furthermore, what appears to be a different
Angel has manifested on the surface.
Please analyze them quickly.
Rei-nyan is gone, so I guess
I'm the only one who's free.
I'll figure it out somehow with Spirit Power!
Shido.
Captain!
We're almost there!
We just need to make it
to that ship called Fraxinus!
Huh?
Is this?
Captain Kusakabe, right?
We heard from Tobiichi.
A-And you are?
Hinako Shizaki, crew member of Fraxinus.
We used our teleporter
to transfer you all into the ship.
Now, bring your soldiers
and Artemisia this way.
Y-Yes.
They're my precious friends.
Please take care of them.
I can't make you any promises,
but we'll do everything we can.
Welcome to Fraxinus.
I'm the commander, Kotori Itsuka.
I'm Ryoko Kusakabe,
former member of the JSDF AST.
Wait!
Y-You're the commander?!
Oh, there's a nostalgic reaction.
We've all gotten used to it,
but normally it would be impossible.
Having a middle school girl
as our commander and all.
Ahem!
Pardon me.
Please forgive me
for foolishly trying to judge your capability
based on your age and appearance.
I'm grateful for your flexibility.
Though I'm sorry we don't have the leeway
to hold a welcoming party
now that you've joined us.
Don't worry about it.
I understand the circumstances.
Thank you.
We've finished retrieving Artemisia.
Kannazuki,
you're all set, aren't you?
We're cutting through.
Yes.
Leave it to me, Commander.
Huh?!
C-Captain Kannazuki!
What are you doing here?!
Ohh, long time no see, Kusakabe.
Kannazuki...
Captain?
He was captain of the AST
when I was first stationed with them!
He was the squad's indisputable top ace.
Wow, that man was?
That's kind of cool, isn't it?
You used to do that, Kannazuki?
I always thought you were just someone
the Commander picked up off the street.
Commander Itsuka, this man is dangerous!
He's the kind of pervert who dreams
about having a middle
school girl kick him in the butt!
He would launch "protect middle school
girls meetings" during our missions,
and when he watched local
middle schoolers going to school
he got reported as a suspicious individual!
You're right in his strike zone, Commander!
How rude!
Lately I prefer them stepping on me
with the heel of their feet!
It's somewhat plain, but quite superb...
We have no time!
MARIA, punch through
the DEM ships ahead of us.
We're launching an attack on Mio.
Roger, authorizing activation of Gungnir.
What are you doing still sleeping?
Ratatoskr doesn't pay you to take naps.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's go, MARIA.
For the sake of the Spirits,
and above all, for more rewards
from our Commander!
Captain...
Are you serious about that guy
being our top ace?
I'm serious.
But that Kyohei Kannazuki was known as
"The Walking HR Complaint"
and "The Man With Valued Skills,
And Criminal Fetishes",
so that Commander is something else
for taming him to this degree.
Launching Yggdrafolium 1 through 15.
I'll drive away the enemy ships before us.
Once we pass through, support the Spirits.
Analysis complete!
Though what is all this?!
What's the matter, Nia?
What's the matter is whatever is
going on with that Angel!
It couldn't be anymore dangerous!
That light causes all living creatures
without exception to die,
and all objects to break.
It's like it's reducing everything's lifespan
or durability to zero in an instant.
To put it simply, it's an instant death beam?
This would definitely get rejected
if it were drawn in a manga.
How are we supposed to defeat that?!
As for the other thing...
It's like that region around her
is a completely different world.
If we got a little closer I might be able
to make out what it's like inside, but...
Kotori, I propose that we
disconnect the sections
containing that unconscious woman we just
received and the non-combatants,
ejecting them to Ulmus.
MARIA...
Of course, I have no intention of losing.
It's merely for risk reduction.
Thank you, MARIA.
For taking initiative to propose it.
No, it's only natural since an AI's
processing speed is faster than humans.
Captain Kusakabe, you've heard the situation.
Could I ask you to guard the ejected sections?
That's...
No, I understand.
Good luck.
Captain, you're a wonderful person.
I definitely want you to work under me.
Now, sorry everyone, but you're
joining me on the path to hell.
If you want to flee, you should
follow those girls right away.
What are you saying, Commander?
After coming this far,
we're with you all the way.
For one thing, it's too dangerous to leave
you alone with the Vice Commander.
I know!
All right.
Then let's go.
I love you all.
Yes!
I've forced our way through
the enemy ships' Territories.
Kotori, ready the main cannon.
I've confirmed what's inside that space!
At the center is Analyst Murasame—
No, Mio Takamiya!
She's fighting Tohka and Tobiichi!
What about the others?!
Around her... Yoshino, Kaguya, Yuzuru,
and Mukuro have fallen!
There are no life signs!
Huh?!
Target: Mio Takamiya.
Gungnir, fire!
What's wrong?
Aren't you coming after me?
If you aren't, then I'll go ahead
and come after you.
Origami!
I know!
Sandalphon!
Einherjar!
Reine.
No, I suppose I should call you Mio?
Either one is fine.
Reine.
Was everything a lie?
The fact that you saved me,
the fact that you kept supporting me,
and the fact that you
called me your best friend.
Were all of those, all of those a lie?
It wasn't a lie.
I treasure all of the Spirits,
and I loved everyone aboard Fraxinus.
And I still consider you
my one and only best friend.
It's just...
I would consume even my best friend
if I must to bring back Shin.
That's all.
How could you?
That's absurd...
Raphael!
Nibeelcole!
Leave it to me, Father!
It's no use!
Well?
It's simple, but it's a not bad move, right?
You've sure had your way with us until now.
So it's time to take responsibility!
Metatron!
Huh? What?
Did he wipe himself out with his own attack?
Maybe he knew he didn't stand a chance
against us and blew himself up?
Hey, hey, Father, what do we do?
Hmm, well...
Huh?!
What?!
What am I doing attacking Father?!
Rebelling? Is it my rebellious phase?
Y-You!
How dare you attack Father looking like me?!
You used Haniel's power
to transform into Nibeelcole?
That's a smart play,
but that also made it easy to predict.
My Demon King, Beelzebub, allows me
to know everything in this world.
So naturally I looked into what kind
of powers each Spirit possessed.
It's about time to draw the curtain on this.
I need to obtain the remaining
Spirit Power before I encounter Deus,
so I can create a new world.
A new world?
Yes.
Me, Elliot, Ellen, and Karen are different
from those manufactured Wizards.
We're the true descendants
of magic users, known as Magi.
Though one day the humans who feared our power
burned down our village and
slaughtered everyone we knew.
That's why we're going to overwrite
this world using Deus' power,
and get our revenge on humanity.
Does that reasoning make it easier to accept?
What?
To be honest, my reason isn't all that grand.
In my case,
my standards for what I find enjoyable and
unpleasant are slightly different from others.
That's all it is.
In all other regards,
I'm not different from others.
I'm just putting in honest effort in pursuit
of my curiosity and the goals I seek.
In that sense, I'm a perfectly average person.
Now, we've talked for long enough.
Farewell, Shido Itsuka,
and
Shinji Takamiya.
Wh-What?!
Natsumi?!
Are you all right, Darling?!
That was close.
You were nearly a goner.
I'm sorry.
You saved me.
What on earth is going on
in this battle right now?!
We've lost contact with everyone else...
Also, isn't that the enemy's leader?
I'll share the details later.
The Spirit of Origin has manifested.
I need to defeat him as quickly as possible
so I can rejoin everyone else!
Wha?! The Spirit of Origin?!
Then we really do need to hurry!
I'm kicking it up for everyone
and you, Darling!
Oh? Diva and Witch, huh?
I'm happy.
I'll be able to obtain two Sephirah too.
What should we do, Darling?
Should we attack the leader while
you take down Nibeelcole?
No.
In order to defeat him,
we'll need an attack he can't predict,
or an attack he can't evade
even if he can predict it.
Both of you enhance me
with Gabriel's performance.
That'll be enough.
Darling?
Sounds like you have a plan.
All right, be careful.
Nothing you do is going to help!
We'll make all three of you
kneel before Father!
Sandalphon!
Halvanhelv!
Father!
Omniscience, the power to know
absolutely everything.
It seems you're still naive
about what that means.
Yeah, I figured you would
block it, knowing you.
You're right that it's only natural
to look up the Angels' power
as soon as you obtained Beelzebub.
And since I'm not the original owner,
of course the power is weakened when I use it.
But you know what,
did you learn this from Beelzebub?
Did you look it up?
Did you, omniscient Westcott?!
What?
Roaring Flash Blast Wave!
Darling!
Shido!
Looks like you've beaten me.
I guess this is the end of the line.
It came surprisingly soon.
Jeez, you surprised me.
Yeah. I thought you would kill him.
Yeah.
I wanted to kill him.
To be honest, I thought he might die
when I fired off that last attack.
That last attack?
That Roaring whatever?
Uhh, ahem.
I'm not really sure what to say about this...
but I think it would be wrong to kill him.
I don't want to be like they were.
Even if I feel bad toward Shinji for that.
Darling.
Well, that's fine too, then.
Are you sure about this?
You'll never get a chance like this again.
Shut up.
The loser doesn't get a say.
You sound just like Elliot.
What a shame.
I was curious what death would feel like too.
Wha?!
Huh?
Miku! Natsumi!
Shin.
Mio!
Wh-Where is everyone...?
I've recovered all the Sephirah.
Along with their lives.
Now we can be together forever, Shin.
Episode 7
The World Tree Sheds Leaves
Episode 8 "The One Who Pulled the Trigger"
Shido is thrown into despair
at the deaths of his friends,
but who appears in that final moment?
Next time is Episode 8:
The One Who Pulled the Trigger.
Wipe away your tears, and fight, Shido.